so meditation number 12 page number six
what's the name of the meditation huh
what's the name of the meditation even
if you ask it not to grow okay so during
this meditation you you have to think
about the Karma
okay of usually the fourth death okay
putting in the habit of achieving the
goals you want and getting in the habit
of stopping the problems you don't want
by using four steps right giving in that
habit is when you call self perpetuating
come on it just gets bigger and bigger
okay the more you use it the more you
want to use it you see that means that
you use it once you make the common to
use it again you use it again you make
the karma to use it twice you'd use it
again you make the common use it four
times and then that special karma of
understanding where things come from
tends to perpetuate itself like the will
of life for negative things okay the
will of life makes negative things
towards four eight sixteen using taking
refuge by using seeds to reach the goals
in your life okay
tends to multiply upon itself okay it's
like double it goes like this
exponential you know it you use it once
suddenly you're using it half the day
suddenly you're using it every day
suddenly you're dreaming about it okay
it's just weird it's a word Karma it's a
cool Karma okay and you can say I'm
tired of thinking about seeds I want to
do something that I'll sneeze
you can't okay okay once you get into it
once you see how cool it is and all your
weird things happen to you supernatural
things supernatural happy things what do
we call it in the mixed nuts group you
start feeling unreasonably happy it's
because this climate tends to when you
call it not just multiply yeah
exponentially increasing if you just try
it a few times it will take over your
life okay and then you can say I don't
want to be happy I don't want to have
finances I don't want to meet new
beautiful people I don't want to live in
a bubble where they put me in the top of
the couch on hotel with the best rock
and roll band in Asia you know I'm sorry
we'll have to go there okay
got it cool okay so when you do that
meditation just think about that okay
you cannot escape what's that expression
in English you can run but you can't
hide there's an English idiom you can
run but you cannot hide the money will
find you that the friends will find you
okay the success will find you okay
darling that's a beautiful meditation